Marcel-André Hille

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Personal Profile

Software engineer with proven full-stack hands-on experience in web development, interactive application development and design thinking.

Skills

Design thinking Kanban & Scrum OOP & SOLID, DRY, KISS React.js, JS, HTML5/CSS3, Sass Node.js, SQL, NoSQL C#, Unity3D Git

Contact Details



+49 (0) 152 275 98 436 maredesign.founder@gmail.com https://github.com/gerinfact

> Johannesstraße 31A 70176 Stuttgart Germany

Experience

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDER GMBH (2019 - PRESENT)

Design, implement & maintain complex web-based applications Conduct agile project management Integrate & maintain database solutions

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

COBRA - COMPUTER'S BRAINWARE GMBH (2018)

Maintain & test CRM desktop application

DIRECTOR OF STUDIES

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2016 - 2018)

Conduct BSc (Hons.) Games Programming Course Build public & business relations

LECTURER OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2016 - present)

Software Architecture, Design Patterns, UX, Game Mathematics, Game AI

Education

WEB DEVELOPMENT & DESIGN

CAREERFOUNDRY (2019 - 2020)

Full-Stack Development & Collaboration

BSC (HONS) GAMES PROGRAMMING, FIRST CLASS

SAE INSTITUTE GMBH (2014 - 2019)

- Academic Excellence Award
- ECTS Grade A

ISA SURF INSTRUCTOR LVL 1

SURFING AUSTRALIA (2013)

Other Projects:

- https://www.maredesin.biz, using HTML5/CSS3, Sass, ES6+
- https://gerinfact.github.io/AP, using HTML5/CSS3, ES6+
- Web Image Trurntable, using HTML5/CSS3, ES6+, Watchify
- Procedural Content Generator, using Unity3D
- BitBoard Game, using Bit Operations in Unity3D
- Game Al driven Android Hack n' Slay Game, using Unity3D
- Ticket management system, using DevExpess & SQL Server
- Database Migrator & Normalizer, using WinForms & SQL
- Games Immersion A Coding Camp for Gamer, founded in 2017